A Guide to the Correspondence and Subject Files of the Commissioner of the Virginia Dept. of Agriculture and Consumer Services, 1984-1994, 2004-2006
Library of Virginia
- Series I. Correspondence and Subject Files, 1984-1994, 2006.
  - 1984-1993 (bulk 1990-1993) (Accession 36853)., 58 cu. ft. (58 boxes)
    - National Association of State Departments of Agriculture (NASDA) - Honor Awards Program, 1990. (Box 49)
    - National Association of State Departments of Agriculture (NASDA) - Committees/Task Forces, 1989-1990. (Box 49)
    - National Association of State Departments of Agriculture (NASDA) - Food Safety Task Force, 1988-1990. (Box 49)
    - National Governor's Association, 1990-1991. (Box 49)
    - National Council of Food Safety, 1990. (Box 49)
    - National Commission on Agriculture and Rural Development Policy, 1985-1991. (Box 49)
    - Nature Conservancy / Heritage Program, 1986-1987. (Box 49)
    - National Egg Pricing System Study Committee, 1982-1984. (Box 49)
    - Organic Food Certification Task Force, 1989-1990. (Box 49)
    - Polish Independant Farmers, Inc., 1989-1990. (Box 49)
    - Agency Head briefing, 1990 Apr. (Box 49)
    - Pesticide Export Reform Act, 1990. (Box 49)
    - Personnel and Training, Dept. of, 1989-1991. (Box 49)
    - Petition - ABC to grant exemption, 1990. (Box 49)
    - Publications - Reduction/Cost savings, 1990. (Box 49)
    - Powell River Project, 1988-1990. (Box 49)
    - Phosphate Ban (S24, H1038), 1987-1988. (Box 50)
    - Planning and Budget, Dept. of, 1988-1991. (Box 50)
    - Potato Certification Plan, 1989-1990. (Box 50)
    - Peanuts (general information), 1990. (Box 50)
    - President Bush's Food Safety Plan, 1989. (Box 50)
    - Patrick County Fruit Growers Coop, 1990. (Box 50)
    - Perdue (general information), 1987-1989. (Box 50)
    - Pay for performance, 1986-1987. (Box 50)
    - Phosphogypsum, 1990. (Box 50)
    - Prompt Payment Act, 1987-1991. (Box 50)
    - Reid Vapor Pressure, 1989-1991. (Box 50)
    - Rail Preservation Policy, 1990. (Box 50)
    - Rural Virginia Development Foundation, 1986-1990. (Box 50)
    - Rural Economic Analysis Program (REAP) Advisory Council, 1990 Jan. (Box 50)
    - Rural Economic Analysis Program (REAP) Education Conference, 1990 Nov. (Box 50)
    - Register of Regulations, 1990. (Box 50)
    - Rights of the Disabled, Dept. of, 1989-1990. (Box 50)
    - Briefing material for Secretary Framme, 1990. (Box 50)
    - Secretary briefing - Long-term goals, 1990. (Box 50)
    - Long-term Economic Development Strategy, 1990. (Box 50)
    - Economic Development Strategic Plan, 1990. (Box 50)
    - Secertary Framme - Visit to the Eastern Shore, 1990. (Box 50)
    - Weekly reports to Secretary Framme, 1990. (Box 50)
    - Economic Development, Dept. of, 1989-1990. (Box 50)
    - EBDC fungicides, 1989-1991. (Box 50)
    - Eating Right campaign, 1990. (Box 50)
    - Farm bill, 1990. (Box 51)
    - Farm Winery Month, 1984-1986. (Box 51)
    - Federal Register, 1990. (Box 51)
    - Food Safety - meeting, 1990 Dec. (Box 51)
    - Federal Crop Insurance Program, 1990-1991. (Box 51)
    - Planning session, 1991 Aug. (Box 51)
    - Division Operating Plans, 1991 June. (Box 51)
    - Agency Strategic Planning session, 1991 July. (Box 51)
    - Strategic Planning Tracking Report, 1991 Nov. (Box 51)
    - Strategic Planning Tracking System, 1990. (Box 51)
    - Strategic Management Team (SMT) - Budget meeting, 1991 Jan. (Box 51)
    - Strategic Management Team (SMT) - Review session, 1990 Nov. (Box 51)
    - VDACS Strategic session, 1988. (Box 51)
    - Information Systems Strategic Planning session, 1991 Mar. (Box 51)
    - Strategic Management Team (SMT) - Agenday setting, 1991 Mar. (Box 51)
    - Exeutive Development, 1991 Mar. (Box 51)
    - Strategic Management Team (SMT) - Fiscal revies, 1991 Mar. (Box 51)
    - Governor's Rural Development Conference, 1990-1991. (Box 51)
    - Strategic Management Team (SMT), 1990-1991. (Box 51)
    - Virginia AG - Chemicals/Soil Fertility, 1989-1990. (Box 52)
    - Virginia Food Dealers Association, 1990-1991. (Box 52)
    - Virginia Executive Institute Alumni, 1988-1990. (Box 52)
    - Virginia Equine Center Foundation, 1989-1990. (Box 52)
    - Virginia District Export Council, 1990-1991. (Box 52)
    - Virginia Agriculture Council, 1989-1990. (Box 52)
    - Virginia's Executive Management letter, 1990. (Box 52)
    - Virginia Business Magazine, 1990. (Box 52)
    - Virginia Christmas Tree Growers Association, 1990. (Box 52)
    - Virginia Farm Bureau Federation, 1989-1990. (Box 52)
    - Virginia Port Authority, 1988-1991. (Box 52)
    - Virginia Partners America, 1990. (Box 52)
    - Virginia Trail Ride, 1990 May. (Box 52)
    - Virginia Vet Medical Association, 1990. (Box 52)
    - VPI and SU, 1989-1990. (Box 52)
    - AgriTech, 1990. (Box 52)
    - Virginia Crop Improvement Association, 1989-1990. (Box 52)
    - Virginia Winegrowers Advisory Board, 1989-1990. (Box 52)
    - Virginia World Trade Association, 1989-1990. (Box 52)
    - NASDA Seattle (VHS), n.d.. (Box 52)
    - USDA Office of Transportation with Southern States "Be Prepared Just in Case - A Guide to Transporting Pesticides (VHS), n.d.. (Box 52)
    - National Farmer's Memorial, Kansas City (VHS), 1989 Nov 9. (Box 52)
    - Virginia Agricultural Computer Council, 1989-1990. (Box 53)
    - Virginia Register, 1990. (Box 53)
    - Virginia Agricultural Development Authority, 1986-1990. (Box 53)
    - Virginia Center for International Business, 1990. (Box 53)
    - Non-tidal Wetlands, 1990. (Box 53)
    - Wetlands, 1990. (Box 53)
    - Virginia World Trade Council - Meeting, 1990 Feb. (Box 53)
    - Virginia World Trade Council - Meeting, 1990 Aug. (Box 53)
    - Wine (Federal Excise Tax), 1990. (Box 53)
    - Washington Farmletter / Kiplinger, 1990. (Box 53)
    - World Food Day, 1990. (Box 53)
    - Williamsburg Winery, 1989-1991. (Box 53)
    - World Trade, Dept. of, 1989-1990. (Box 53)
    - Watermelon Board, 1989-1990. (Box 53)
    - Administration and Planning, Division of, 1990. (Box 53)
    - Virginia Dept. of Agriculture and Consumer Services (VDACS) Board - Meeting, 1990 May. (Box 53)
    - Strategic Planning Session, 1990 Apr. (Box 53)
    - Board of Agriculture and Consumer Services - Appointments, 1989-1991. (Box 54)
    - Board of Agriculture and Consumer Services - Correspondence, 1990. (Box 54)
    - Board of Agriculture and Consumer Services - Correspondence, 1991. (Box 54)
    - Board of Agriculture and Consumer Services - Meeting, 1990 Feb. (Box 54)
    - Board of Agriculture and Consumer Services - Meeting, 1990 July. (Box 54)
    - Board of Agriculture and Consumer Services - Meeting, 1990 Aug. (Box 54)
    - Board of Agriculture and Consumer Services - Meeting, 1990 Sept. (Box 54)
    - Board of Agriculture and Consumer Services - Meeting, 1990 Dec. (Box 54)
    - Board of Agriculture and Consumer Services - Meeting, 1991 Feb. (Box 54)
    - Board of Agriculture and Consumer Services - Meeting, 1991 May. (Box 54)
    - Board of Agriculture and Consumer Services - Meeting, 1991 July. (Box 54)
    - Board of Agriculture and Consumer Services - Meeting, 1991 Oct. (Box 54)
    - Board of Agriculture and Consumer Services - Report to the Governor, 1990. (Box 54)
    - Board of Agriculture and Consumer Services - Report to the Governor, 1991. (Box 54)
    - Board of Agriculture and Consumer Services - Strategic Plan, 1990. (Box 54)
    - Board of Agriculture and Consumer Services - Strategic Planning Meeting, 1990 Mar. (Box 54)
    - Statistics, 1990. (Box 54)
    - Virginia's Finest - Program Bullets, 1990 July. (Box 54)
    - HJR 434 Cornstarch (Biodegradable), 1989. (Box 54)
    - Budget Concerns/Amendments, 1990. (Box 54)
    - HJR 363 Improving Rural Economy, 1989. (Box 54)
    - HJR 395 Use of Composted Waste, 1988. (Box 54)
    - SJR 155 Study of Hazardous Material, 1989. (Box 54)
    - HJR 300 Farm Labor Study, 1989. (Box 54)
    - SJR 131 Credit Card Fraud Study, 1990. (Box 54)
    - HJR Promote Rural Economy, 1990. (Box 54)
    - Legislative Studies, 1989. (Box 55)
    - Legislative Studies, 1990. (Box 55)
    - Equine Specialist, 1990. (Box 55)
    - International Center / Forest Products, 1989-1990. (Box 55)
    - International Marketing (Rich), 1990. (Box 55)
    - Marketing, Division of #2 (Gomperts), 1990 June-Dec. (Box 55)
    - Virginia Farmers #10, 1989-1991. (Box 55)
    - Meeting - Gordon Murchie - Wine, 1990 Mar. (Box 55)
    - Meeting - Gomperts/Rich, 1990 Mar. (Box 55)
    - Meeting - Chip Planck/Gus Schumacher, 1990. (Box 55)
    - Commodity Boards - J.P. Welch, 1989-1990. (Box 55)
    - Virginia's Finest Consumer Awareness Survey, 1990. (Box 55)
    - Virginia's Finest Participant Survey, 1990. (Box 55)
    - Lazarus at the Gate, 1990. (Box 55)
    - Food Distribution (Nelson), 1989-1990. (Box 55)
    - Apple and Peach Tree Survey, 1990-1991. (Box 55)
    - Virginia Wholesale Farmers Market, 1985. (Box 55)
    - Marketing Participation - State Fair, 1990. (Box 55)
    - James City County Grower's Coop, 1988-1991. (Box 56)
    - Central Virginia Farmers Market, 1990. (Box 56)
    - Virginia's Finest - Progress Reports, 1990. (Box 56)
    - Peter Wong, 1990-1991. (Box 56)
    - Direct Farmers Market (Position), 1990. (Box 56)
    - Programmer Analyst Position, 1990. (Box 56)
    - Farmers Direct Marketing Association, 1990. (Box 56)
    - Direct Marketing, 1990. (Box 56)
    - Economic/Marketing Research Office, 1989-1990. (Box 56)
    - Livestock/Dairy/Poultry, 1990. (Box 56)
    - Product/Industry Regulation Division #2, 1990-1991. (Box 56)
    - Policy Analysis/Development (Tubbs), 1990. (Box 56)
    - HJR 391 Public Knowledge Gypsy Moth, 1990-1991. (Box 56)
    - VDOT/VDACS Agreement re: Seed Samples, 1990. (Box 56)
    - Varroa Mite (parasite of honey bees), 1990. (Box 56)
    - Nursery Inspection Fee Increase, 1989-1990. (Box 56)
    - Monsanto - Genetically Engineered Soybeans, 1990. (Box 56)
    - Fire Ants (Imported), 1990. (Box 56)
    - Agriculture Products Licensing/Bonding Law, 1989-1990. (Box 56)
    - Cozart Tobacco, Pennington Gap, 1990. (Box 56)
    - Gypsy Moth, 1990. (Box 56)
    - Johnson Grass #5, 1990. (Box 56)
    - National Weights and Measures Week, 1990. (Box 56)
    - Van Kesteren Farms, Tasley, Va., 1990. (Box 56)
    - Seed Industry - Meeting, 1990. (Box 56)
    - Endophyte Problem in Tall Fescue, 1990. (Box 56)
    - Weather Crop Reports, 1990. (Box 56)
    - Soybean Variety/Cropping Practice Survey, 1990. (Box 56)
    - New Performance System Briefing, 1990. (Box 57)
    - Information Systems, 1990-1991. (Box 57)
    - Office of Communications (Altschul), 1990. (Box 57)
    - Strategic Planning (Hill), 1990. (Box 57)
    - Human Resource Office, 1990. (Box 57)
    - Internal Audit Director (Hazelwood), 1990. (Box 57)
    - Strategic Planning Meeting (Don), 1989 Aug. (Box 57)
    - FIMS Information/Agreement, 1990. (Box 57)
    - Performance Reveiwers, 1990. (Box 57)
    - VDACS Organization Charts, 191. (Box 57)
    - Animal Health, Div. of (Miller), 1990. (Box 57)
    - Lead Poisoning in Veal Calves, 1990. (Box 57)
    - Meat/Poultry Inspection - Meetings, 1990-1991. (Box 57)
    - CEO/Poultry Companies, 1990. (Box 57)
    - Meat/Poultry Inspection, 1990. (Box 57)
    - Animal Welfare Issues, 1990-1991. (Box 57)
    - Carroll Foods, 1990. (Box 57)
    - Mecklenburg County Investigations, 1990. (Box 57)
    - Mid-Atlantic Poultry Health Council, 1989-1990. (Box 57)
    - Equine Encephalitis Virus, 1989-1990. (Box 58)
    - Mid-Atlantic Poultry, 1990 May. (Box 58)
    - Disposal of Dead Poultry, 1990. (Box 58)
    - Animal Health Advisory Council, 1990. (Box 58)
    - Fee Structure - Animal Health Lab, 1990. (Box 58)
    - Meat Inspection Program, 1990. (Box 58)
    - National Consumer Week, 1988-1990. (Box 58)
    - Consumer Affairs, Div. of (Blakemore), 1990. (Box 58)
    - Dairy and Foods, Div. of (Holliday), 1990. (Box 58)
    - Light (Non-Fat) Ice Cream, 1990. (Box 58)
    - Meeting with Dell Aria re: Dioxin, 1990. (Box 58)
    - Christine Solem - Goat Milk, 1990. (Box 58)
    - Food Service Advisory Committee, 1990. (Box 58)
    - Bowman Apple Products, 1990. (Box 58)
    - Soup Tampering Incident, 1990. (Box 58)
  - 1969-1991 (bulk 1989-1990) (Accession 37349)., 135 cu. ft. (135 boxes)
    - NASDA Proceedings, 1989. (Box 59)
    - SAC Agricultrue and Rural Development, 1989. (Box 59)
    - Farm credit (general information), 1988-1990. (Box 59)
    - Farm Supplies Cooperatives (general information), 1988. (Box 59)
    - Food Security Act of 1985, 1985-1987. (Box 59)
    - Food Safety Issues, 1989. (Box 59)
    - Groundwater (general information), 1988-1990. (Box 59)
    - Governor's Trip to Europe, 1989. (Box 59)
    - Governor's Work Weeks (May-June), 1988-1989. (Box 59)
    - Governor's Agricultural Advisory Board, undated. (Box 59)
    - Governor's Meeting - Black Leadership, 1988-1989. (Box 59)
    - General Services, Dept. of, 1988-1989. (Box 59)
    - Governor's Office, 1989. (Box 59)
    - Gubernatorial Candidates (general information), 1989. (Box 59)
    - Gasohol Tax Incentives (OEES), 1984-1986. (Box 59)
    - German Tobacco Sales Mission, 1988. (Box 59)
    - Hearing Officers, Utilization of, 1988-1989. (Box 59)
    - Hardwood Export Trade Council, 1986. (Box 59)
    - Hydrilla - Potomac River, 1984-1989. (Box 59)
    - Litter/Waste - Poultry Disposal, 1987. (Box 59)
    - Interbuild Trade Show, 1988-1989. (Box 59)
    - Isner, Kenneth W., 1988-1989. (Box 59)
    - Information Technology, Dept. of, 1989. (Box 59)
    - State Departments/Institutions, 1987-1989. (Box 59)
    - JLARC Study - Economic Development, 1989. (Box 59)
    - James Madison University (JMU) - International Internship Advisory Council, 1989. (Box 59)
    - King William County (New Industry), 1989. (Box 59)
    - Legislative Services, Dept. of, 1984-1988. (Box 59)
    - Minorities and Women - Governor's Program, 1988. (Box 59)
    - Migrant Housing Study (HJR 117), 1988-1989. (Box 59)
    - Migrant Labor Laws (Project), 1988-1989. (Box 59)
    - National Agricultural Chemical Association, 1989-1990. (Box 59)
    - NASDA Conference, 1989 Mar. (Box 59)
    - NASDA - RJR Nabisco Award, 1987-1988. (Box 60)
    - NASDA Conference, 1989 Mar. (Box 60)
    - NASDA - Resolutions and Procedures Review, 1989. (Box 60)
    - NASDA - Food and Agriculture Expo, 1989. (Box 60)
    - NASDA - Conference, 1989 Sept. (Box 60)
    - NASDA - Resolution, 1989. (Box 60)
    - NASDA - Washington Office Reports, 1988-1989. (Box 60)
    - NASDA - Resolution, 1989. (Box 60)
    - NASDA - Honor Awards Program, 1983-1989. (Box 60)
    - NASDA/USDA - Task Force, 1989 Aug. (Box 60)
    - NASDA - Province Accord, 1989. (Box 60)
    - NASDA - Board Meeting, 1989 Nov. (Box 60)
    - NASDA - US Potato Coordination Team, 1989. (Box 60)
    - National Governors Association, 1988-1990. (Box 60)
    - Nursery Survey, 1988-1990. (Box 60)
    - Football/Basketball/Softball information, 1982-1988. (Box 60)
    - EEO (Re-evaluate in six months), undated. (Box 60)
    - VDACS Overview, 1989-1990. (Box 60)
    - VDACS Classification Regrades, 1989. (Box 60)
    - VDACS Audit FY 1987-1988, 1987-1988. (Box 60)
    - VDACS Audit FY 1988-1989, 1988-1989. (Box 60)
    - VDACS Audit FY 1989-1990, 1989-1990. (Box 60)
    - VDACS Continual Audit, 1989-1991. (Box 60)
    - Speakers Bureau, 1990-1991. (Box 60)
    - VDACS Organization Chart, 1989. (Box 60)
    - VDACS Fall Conference, 1990. (Box 60)
    - EEO Advisory Committee, 1986-1991. (Box 61)
    - NASDA Thank You Letters, 1990. (Box 61)
    - Flower Fund, 1984-1990. (Box 61)
    - Regulatory Management Classification, 1989. (Box 61)
    - Public Relations Plan, 1988. (Box 61)
    - NASDA Board meeting and minutes, 1969-1974. (Box 61)
    - Consumer Affairs, Division of (Blakemore), 1990. (Box 61)
    - NASDA Washington Office (Grant), 1989-1990. (Box 61)
    - Disaster Assistance - Fruit Crops, 1990-1991. (Box 61)
    - Reports of Audit, 1987. (Box 61)
    - Economic Development, Secretary of, 1990 Jan-Apr. (Box 62)
    - Economic Development, Secretary of, 1990 Apr-Sept. (Box 62)
    - Marketing Packet, 1990. (Box 62)
    - Marketing, Division of, 1990 Jan-Apr. (Box 62)
    - Marketing, Division of, 1990 Apr-Sept. (Box 62)
    - Consolidated Laboratory Advisory Board, 1989 May. (Box 62)
    - Consolidated Laboratory Advisory Board, 1989 Oct. (Box 62)
    - DCLS New Technology Symposium, 1987-1989. (Box 62)
    - Council on the Environment (2 binders), 1989. (Box 62)
    - Council on the Environment, 1989-1990. (Box 62)
    - Chesapeake Bay National Estuarine, 1988-1990. (Box 62)
    - Council of State Governments, 1989. (Box 62)
    - Commonwealth Management Institute, 1988-1991. (Box 62)
    - Center for Agricultureal and Rural Development, 1989. (Box 62)
    - Comptroller, Office of the, 1989. (Box 62)
    - Connectivity Project, 1988. (Box 62)
    - Council on Information Management, 1989-1990. (Box 62)
    - Chesapeake Bay (general info), 1989. (Box 63)
    - Consolidated Lab Services Advisory Board, 1989. (Box 63)
    - Census, Bureau of, 1989. (Box 63)
    - Combined Charitable Campaign, 1988-1989. (Box 63)
    - Drug-free Workplace Act, 1989. (Box 63)
    - Direct deposit, 1989. (Box 63)
    - Equine Census / Economic Development, 1989. (Box 63)
    - Economic Development Mission, 1989. (Box 63)
    - Economic Development, Secretary of, 1989 Jan-June. (Box 63)
    - Economic Development, Secretary of, 1989 Aug-Dec. (Box 63)
    - Economic Development, Secretary of, 1989. (Box 63)
    - Meeting with Secretary Roberts, 1989 July. (Box 63)
    - Economic / Trade Activities/Updates, 1988-1989. (Box 63)
    - Export Enhancement Program - USDA, 1987-1990. (Box 63)
    - Emergency Services, Dept. of, 1988-1991. (Box 63)
    - Freedom of Information/Conflict of Interest, 1989-1990. (Box 63)
    - Food and Drug Administration, 1989. (Box 63)
    - Farm bill, 1990. (Box 63)
    - Odor Standards, 1989. (Box 64)
    - Organic Food Certification Task Force, 1989. (Box 64)
    - Organic Food Certification Task Force - Scoping session, 1989 Dec. (Box 64)
    - Organic Food Certification Task Force - Certification Program, 1989. (Box 64)
    - Organic Food Act, 1989-1990. (Box 64)
    - Oil Overcharge #2, 1989. (Box 64)
    - Oil/Hazardous Material Pollution, 1989. (Box 64)
    - Peanuts (general info), 1988-1990. (Box 64)
    - Personnel and Training, Dept. of, 1988-1989. (Box 64)
    - Potato Promotion, 1989. (Box 64)
    - Rural Economic Analysis Program (REAP) Conference, 1989 Nov. (Box 64)
    - Rural Economic Analysis Program (REAP) Presentation, 1989 July. (Box 64)
    - Rural Economic Analysis Program (REAP) Advisory Council, 1989-1990. (Box 64)
    - Rural Virginia, Inc., 1989. (Box 64)
    - Rappahannock River Basin Advisory Committee, 1989. (Box 64)
    - Rural Development / Capacity Building, 1989. (Box 64)
    - Rural Virginia Development Foundation Board, 1989. (Box 64)
    - Rural Partnership Act, 1989. (Box 64)
    - State Fair Agriculture Council, 1989. (Box 64)
    - State Radiation Advisory Council, 1986-1990. (Box 64)
    - State Land Evaluation Advisory Council, 1990. (Box 64)
    - State Land Evaluation Advisory Council, 1987-1989. (Box 64)
    - Soviet Union (general info), 1989. (Box 64)
    - Southwest Virginia Diversification, 1988-1991. (Box 65)
    - Salmonella Enteritidis, 1988-1989. (Box 65)
    - Soviet briefing, 1989. (Box 65)
    - State Rail Advisory Committee, 1988-1990. (Box 65)
    - Soil and Water Conservation Board, Virginia, 1989. (Box 65)
    - NASDA, 1989. (Box 65)
    - SASDA (general info), 1989. (Box 65)
    - SASDA - Winter meeting, 1989. (Box 65)
    - Southeastern US Trade Association (SUSTA), 1979-1991. (Box 65)
    - International Food and Agriculture Trade Show, 1980. (Box 65)
    - Committee to find replacement for stone, 1981. (Box 65)
    - Southeastern US Trade Association (SUSTA), 1981. (Box 65)
    - Southeastern US Trade Association (SUSTA), 1988. (Box 65)
    - Southeastern US Trade Association (SUSTA) - Program Plans, 1976-1980. (Box 65)
    - Southeastern US Trade Association (SUSTA) - Bylaws Review Committee, 1978-1979. (Box 65)
    - Southeastern US Trade Association (SUSTA), 1989. (Box 66)
    - Southeastern US Trade Association (SUSTA), 1990-1991. (Box 66)
    - Southeastern US Trade Association (SUSTA) - Sweet Potato Promotion, 19. (Box 66)
    - Southeastern US Trade Association (SUSTA) - Anugg Trade Show, 1977. (Box 66)
    - Southeastern US Trade Association (SUSTA) - Conference, 1976. (Box 66)
    - Environment / Agriculture Issues, 1988-1989. (Box 66)
    - Virginia Personnel Act (SB 643), 1990. (Box 66)
    - Selective Restrictions, 1991. (Box 66)
    - VDACS - Executive Staff Minutes, 1988-1989. (Box 66)
    - VDACS - Athletics Committee, 1988. (Box 66)
    - VDACS - Conservation Planning Campaign, 1990. (Box 66)
    - VDACS - Vacant Positions, 1990. (Box 66)
    - VDACS - Efficiency Study, 1989-1990. (Box 66)
    - VDACS - Master Calendar, 1990. (Box 66)
    - VDACS - Building Committee, 1989-1990. (Box 66)
    - VDACS - Emergency Evacuation, 1988-191. (Box 66)
    - VDACS - Transportation Committee, 1990. (Box 66)
    - VDACS - Logo, 1989-1991. (Box 66)
    - VDACS - Space Needs / Space Study, 1988-1990. (Box 66)
    - VDACS - Exhbit Committee, 1977-1991. (Box 66)
    - Virginia Agriculture Council, 1988 May. (Box 66)
    - Virginia Agriculture Council, 1988 Aug. (Box 66)
    - Virginia Agriculture Council, 1988 Nov. (Box 66)
    - Virginia Agriculture Council, 1987-1988. (Box 66)
    - Virginia Agriculture Council, 1988. (Box 66)
    - Virginia Agriculture Council, 1989. (Box 66)
    - Virginia Agriculture Council, 1983-1991. (Box 67)
    - Virginia Agriculture Credit Committee, 1987-1990. (Box 67)
    - Chippokes Plantation Farm Foundation, 1989-1991. (Box 67)
    - Agriculture and Consumer Services, Board of, 1992 July. (Box 67)
    - Administration, Divison of, 1988-1989. (Box 68)
    - Strategic Session, 1989 June. (Box 68)
    - Strategic Planning Director, 1989. (Box 68)
    - Crisis Communication Plan, 1989. (Box 68)
    - Training/EEO Officer, 1989. (Box 68)
    - Regrade, 1989. (Box 68)
    - Internal Auditor, 1989. (Box 68)
    - Personnel Director, 1989. (Box 68)
    - Animal Health, Division of, 1989. (Box 68)
    - Avian Flu, 1989. (Box 68)
    - Equine Infectious Anema Committee, 1989. (Box 68)
    - Meat and Poultry Inspection - USCA, 1989. (Box 68)
    - Consumer Affairs, Division of (#1), 1989. (Box 68)
    - Consumer Affairs, Division of (#2), 1989. (Box 68)
    - Communications Office, 1989. (Box 68)
    - Northern Virginia Consumer Affairs Office, 1989. (Box 68)
    - Dairy and Foods, Division of, 1989. (Box 68)
    - Hepatitis A, 1989. (Box 68)
    - Buttery - Food Service Certification, 1989. (Box 68)
    - National Fisheries Institute, 1989. (Box 68)
    - Seafood Council, 1989. (Box 68)
    - International Marketing, 1989. (Box 68)
    - Equine Quarantine, 1989. (Box 68)
    - Virginia Leading Agriculture Exports, 1989. (Box 69)
    - Peter Law, 1988-1989. (Box 69)
    - International Marketing Progress Study, 1989. (Box 69)
    - Chicken feet, 1989. (Box 69)
    - Forest Products Mission - Carribean, 1989-1990. (Box 69)
    - Marketing, Division of (#1), 1989. (Box 69)
    - Marketing, Division of (#2), 1989. (Box 69)
    - Virginia's Finest Program (#2), 1989-1990. (Box 69)
    - Economic Research Unit, 1989. (Box 69)
    - Virginia Direct Marketing Conference, 1988-1989. (Box 69)
    - Wine Marketing Specialist, 1989. (Box 69)
    - Dedication - Southwest Farmers Market, 1989. (Box 69)
    - Farmers Market Board, 1988-1989. (Box 69)
    - Virginia's Farmers Market (#9), 1989. (Box 69)
    - Farmers Market Board (#8), 1989. (Box 69)
    - Policy Analysis and Development, 1989. (Box 69)